The End Hey!
You won't find a better deal, Signore!
The other guy said the same thing.
Well, I'll throw in a
personal tour of the city.
Huh?
Seriously?
What a character! What?
Where did it go?
What's wrong?
My back disappeared!
Huh? As agreed.
So then, there anything
I should know about?
Not a thing.
Thanks to you.
Is that right?
I'll be off, then.
This is what you wanted, right?
Yeah, that's the stuff.
But the thing is, this is all the
money I could scrounge together.
In that case, I guess this is all you get.
The Jewel of Southern Italy, Napoli.
It's a city so beautiful, a single
visit can satisfy the soul unto death.
Or so the saying goes.
Excuse me!
Do you know how we can get
to the Church of Santa Char?
Oh, Santa Char, you say?
You're going to want to keep straight.
Then at the first signal, you...
I knew it!
The Church is that way!
Okay, you're right.
Thank you very much for your help.
Are you all right, miss?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for catching me.
Sorry for bumping into you.
Just watch where you're going next time.
Let's take off. Hey, miss.
You must have dropped this.
No way!
Oh my gosh, you're the best!
Happy to help.
Wow, talk about Mr.
Sweep you off your feet.
I should have snuck a pig with that Code.
Bizarre.
Did they just fly out of my bag?
I thought they landed there and flew off.
Probably right.
Here in Napoli, vigilance
is a prized virtue.
Excuse me, I'll take a
chocolado and pistachio, please.
Huh?
Make it two. Va Bone.
Come on, people!
No license, no work!
Don't make me say it again!
Get a move on, would ya?
Cut, so. Hey!
You only moved one time down!
There, you see?
A mess.
I can bypass that.
What do you think?
They're in a cheaper way downtown. Yeah.
Yeah?
What do you call cheap?
Luca!
Did you forget?
You fork over the street tax you
owe me before doing business.
Mercy, please!
I thought I was pretty clear.
Taxes first, then work. But...
But what, Ted man?
But I've got a family to feed.
Oh.
Please, no!
I'd like to say I feel for you, guy,
but friendship is thicker than blood.
Got it?
If you want me, you won't know who
else is dealing behind your back!
Name.
Give me the rat bastard's name.
It's Giorno!
Giorno Giovanna!
Giorno?
Yeah, and the kid's been
making a killer too!
So that's how it is.
Thanks.
The info's much appreciated.
Hey, Buster!
Did you hear what I just said?
No license, no work!
Keep it moving! Buongiorno!
I finally made it.
What a journey.
I'm definitely not in Japan anymore.
Okay, let's get down to business.
Haruno Shiobana.
That's not a name you hear every day.
I should head for the hotel.
I can't track this guy down
carrying my bags around with me.
All right, now to find a taxi
stand. Damn! Look at him go!
I know, I can't think of anyone who
can futz with their ear like that.
It's one hell of a crazy trick.
How is he even doing that?
Gross! That's foul.
How'd this guy fold in
his entire ear? Wow.
Gotta say, kid, that
just made my whole day.
Crazy.
Just keep it on the down low, yeah?
You stay weird now.
Need a taxi?
No, no, I'm fine, really, thank you.
Are you sure?
I'll drop you off for 180,000 lira.
That's a pretty sweet deal.
And I can at least get
you to the center of town.
Let's see now.
So the conversion would be about
10,000 yen. Not interested.
That's double the going rate, buddy!
Wow, nice job.
You speak excellent Italian.
Huh?
Have you ever lived here in Italy?
Oh, no, I just had my friend
Rohan sensei make it so...
N-never mind that, it's not important.
So, are you really willing
to drive me to town?
I mean, you look like you're in junior
high or high school at the very most.
And what exactly was that
thing you handed to the guard?
I'm pretty sure I saw cash.
Did you pay them off?
No, it's nothing like that.
Don't bust a gasket.
So, 10,000 lira then, and forget the tip.
Let's get going before it gets late.
Wait, isn't 10,000 lira 500 yen?
Uh, that won't be necessary.
I'll just wait like everyone else.
Still want to wait?
10,000, you said? That's right.
Trade-off is you have to
carry your own luggage.
You don't have to tip, remember?
Bags up front, you're taking
the luxury spot, the back seat.
I should warn you in advance.
I'm not some naive Japanese tourist, so
you'd better not try anything funny, got it?
I expect this car to head
straight to my hotel.
Certo, you want me to go
straight to your hotel.
Sounds good, though your bags
will be empty on arrival.
What the? He left?
Why would he take off
before I could get in?
Hey, pretend you didn't see.
Shit, no, no, no, come back.
Ciao for now.
Reverb, act three!
It didn't have to end this way.
I told you, don't try
to pull anything funny.
I'm not gonna stop you from running.
Once I grab my belongings,
we'll be all done here.
Look at him go!
Giorno must have botched the job!
What did the kid expect scamming a Japanese
tourist when he's half Japanese himself?
But with that hair color and
a name like Giorno Giovanna,
who'd ever guess he doesn't have
a drop of Italian blood in him?
There's no way...
What?
It's all gone! How?
It's like some kind of weird egg.
Is this thing a stand?
Why would one show up the
moment I touched down in Italy?
I must have been out of my mind.
That's not a stand, it's
a living, breathing thing.
Creepy tree frog aside, how'd
my suitcase just disappear?
There's no way he could
have hidden it that fast.
Uh, what's happening?
I've got to get some answers.
Uh, Scusi?
Can you tell me anything
about that cab driver?
Any minute now.
You're Giorno Giovanna, right?
We haven't met before, have we?
Giorno, you have any clue who I am?
Leaky Eye Luca.
You were in a dispute a while
back, and when it turned ugly,
you took a knife to the face, but kept
fighting and swinging to spite your wound.
The complications from that little scrap
left you with a perpetually leaking eye,
hence your moniker.
Here, take a load off and
make yourself comfortable.
What's the holdup? Pop a squat.
Looking up at you is
hurting my eyes so how old
are you 15 and change
what Really haha you're a
baby so here's the thing
Giorno any true friendship
has to Be built on the
firm foundation of the
three T's you've heard
of them haven't You in
case you're drawing a blank
the first one is truth
the second one is Tolerance
last but not least you
have the third T tribute
and Fool the three T's
Of true friendship was
there something you needed
I wasn't finished showing
you The rope so shut
your face hole nobody said
you could ask questions
drones all As for what I
needed I hear you started
a hustle at the airport
huh surely you Can see
how this would be
confusing after all I don't
remember receiving any
Tribute from you and without
tribute how could we remain
true friends now hand
over your wallet.
Signore, you've got it wrong.
I've already paid your tribute.
I don't have any money.
You talking about that, guard?
You have to be a special kind of stupid
to think I'm working with that old...
Huh?
What the hell is this?
A family photo?
I know you're holding out on me,
so fork over the cash right now, blondie.
Signore Luca, I really hate
having to repeat myself.
And as I've already said, I
don't owe you anything. Huh?
Now please don't make
me say it a third time.
Test to the castle!
Time out, kid.
What the hell is that?
So he came back. Flick it off!
No, the frog has nothing to do with this.
Please don't ask me to do that.
That wasn't a freaking suggestion, Amiko!
And you still haven't
paid the taxes you owe!
Are you seriously gonna
refuse both of my orders?
You've got some brass balls, kid!
No one says no to leaky-eyed Leaky twice!
This frog is a living creature
with a will of his own.
He thinks and acts for himself.
Let's go our separate ways.
You're really starting to piss me off.
Flicking him off is
something I just can't do.
Just shut your damn mouth already! Stop!
He's harmless if you leave him alone!
Get ready to die, you insubordinate dick!
Don't say I didn't try to warn you.
This little guy here isn't totally loyal
to me, as you're about to find out.
Just remember, he's
only protecting himself,
as anyone would protect
something as precious as life.
Do you get it now?
An attack on him is an attack
on oneself, and a fatal one.
But bear this in mind,
I asked you very nicely not to
make me repeat myself a third time.
Repeating oneself is futile.
It's a big waste of time,
and a bigger waste of breath.
Totally useless.
You want me to get a skin
sample from this kid?
That's right.
Send it to me as soon as it's secured.
The Speedwagon Foundation will
examine his genetic makeup.
His DNA?
What's so special about him?
Let's just say that his dead father
was unique, hence the analysis.
I don't need much to begin.
An epidermal sample will suffice.
That's the rundown.
I'll cover your travel expenses. What?
You're covering them all?
That's sort of eerie.
About this kid, not to sound weird, but he
bears a really strong resemblance to you.
The address written on this photo
should be around here somewhere.
They should watch that.
There's no reason for you to be concerned.
No one around here would be
foolish enough to steal their bag.
Not if they wanted to live.
Wow, that's impressive.
This area must be pretty safe, huh?
Signore, how about some lunch?
Thanks for the offer, but I'll pass.
Don't you want to drink with me?
I promise you won't regret it.
I'll pay for it.
How about no?
Can I come?
Now all of you just go
away and leave me be. Okay.
Ademani journal. Ciao now.
It's the guy from before!
Huh?
I finally found you, you lousy crook!
That's my money you got!
You!
How'd you know I was here?
Where the heck is my passport
and what did you do with my bags?
It really pains me to have to tell
you this, But your stuff is gone.
I sold it.
Sorry, Amiko.
Now you know, so stop chasing me.
You're not getting away again!
What's weighing down my hand?
So earlier, that wasn't
the car malfunctioning?
This stranger, could he have
the same kind of powers as me?
Hang on, what did he just say?
Golden wind!
End!
Plant the seed of vitality.
Bring forth new life.
There was something there, I'm sure of it.
Act three, go!
The target has vanished. Damn that guy.
How'd he manage to break free from
three freezes pressure grip so easily?
I'll say it again.
I strongly suggest you
abandon following me.
I despise saying something a second
time when once is sufficient.
Repetition is the very
essence of futility.
Some friendly advice for you, stranger.
Try not to lead a useless life.
Take him down, Act Three,
before he gets away!
The force ricocheted back to me
when I hit the tree, but why?
I stole all your belongings.
Yet you still held back
when you attacked me.
Your injuries tell me everything
I need to know about you.
You, Amiko, have a good soul.
There's no doubt about it.
Giorno Giovanna.
That kid is a stand user.
Hello.
Jotaro, it's Koichi.
Ah, good to hear from you.
Did you make it to Italy? I found him.
The kid you asked me to look into.
Haruno Shibana.
That was record time.
Yeah, well I hope you're
holding onto your hat.
I ran into him at the airport.
And we kind of had it out.
But now we have confirmation.
He's a stand user and a strong one.
He goes by Giorno Giovanna here.
It's just like you said, Mr.
Jotaro.
Stand users are somehow
drawn to each other.
Our meeting was completely by chance.
He looks like a student, but acts
like he's in some sort of gang.
He stole my bag and all my money.
And then there's his stand ability.
Seems like he can reflect attacks
right back at the attacker.
I'm sorry about all the trouble.
I'll get you a room and some money.
Just hang tight.
Thank you, Mr.
Jotaro.
Oh, and the picture's outdated.
He's blonde now.
I spoke to some people who know him,
and they said he didn't dye his hair.
It just changed, and recently, too.
This is probably a sensitive subject,
but you mentioned his father
when I started all this.
Mr.
Jotaro, are you two related somehow?
His father and I go way back.
I'm the one who killed him.
His name was Dio Brando.
Did you say Dio?
As in the bow and arrow, Dio?
The very one.
I learned this year that Dio
may have fathered a child.
I needed to uncover the truth.
I had to know whether Giorno Giovanna
was Dio's son, and if he was,
how much he took after his father.
But didn't Dio's body
once belong to a Joestar?
You said he has blonde hair now.
Be careful.
That may be proof that Dio's blood has
only recently awakened his stand power.
Something must have triggered it.
There's a good chance a powerful
stand user has arrived in Naples.
Man, just what we didn't need.
You've been through enough already,
so keep your distance from this kid.
Got it?
One last thing.
Do you think he's a true enemy?
More to the point, could he be an ally?
What does your gut say?
You're the only one who's met him.
How'd he come across?
I can't say for sure, but there was a...
How do I put this?
He had a certain eloquence about him.
Is this yours? It's not.
Hmm, I see.
It's my lucky day.
Tell me, if you were to
find a bag on this tram,
a bag that had a billion lira
inside, would you turn it in?
You're joking, right?
It's finder's keepers.
At least you're honest.
But what if I was really an undercover
cop, and I saw the whole thing?
Ah,
well in that case, I'd let you mosey off
with half the money to look the other way.
Probably.
Now that's the spirit.
And you know, I get the
sense you really would.
The look on your face isn't the
expression of a bluffing man.
I can clearly see that
you're telling the truth.
You see, I have a special knack for
telling whether someone's being truthful.
And I don't often make mistakes.
Have you ever noticed how the
face often glistens with sweat?
That's normally the first tell.
But what's important
is the sweat's flavor.
That's the telltale sign.
Shuichi, who exactly are you?
Leaky Iluca got his head bashed
in with his own shovel and was
conveniently found unconscious
on the outskirts of the airport.
He's critical and it's looking
like he's never going to come too.
And I've come here to
hunt down the culprit.
So let's talk.
No one has the slightest idea why
Leaky Iluca was even at the airport.
However,
I spoke with a security
guard and was told that
a young man named Giorno
Giovanna was there.
If it's not too much trouble, I thought
we'd have a quick chat about the matter.
Chat, huh?
You a cop or what?
Don't be ridiculous.
Luca wasn't some ordinary street punk.
He was a mafioso, and several
people had reason to off him.
He had a special knack for being hated.
Problem is, that's not how his boss
is electing to see the situation.
A member of the Family has been slain,
and what honor he had has
been severely compromised.
He's ordered me to find the perpetrator,
and sort out everything
surrounding this mess.
Make this easy and cooperate.
Understand?
Did you meet up with Leaky
Ailuka at the airport? Leaky who?
Never heard of him.
You're not perspiring.
Right then, that's all I need.
You're in the clear.
Sorry to bother you, Giorno Giovanna.
What the hell is going on?
And why was my fist clenched?
You're looking at Luca's right eye.
It's not currently in use, so
I thought I'd bring it along.
What a surprise.
That's the distinct tang of a liar.
Right, Giorno Giovanna?
I have to apologize.
I know I said we were done with questions,
but it seems the game has changed a bit.
Wouldn't you agree, Giorno?
I now know you're a liar,
but the question is why.
Don't be shy, Amico.
I'm really very interested in
hearing what you have to say.
What's with you all?
Jealous or something?
I'll gladly let you in on this.
You can call me Bruno Bucciarati.
Time for the truth.
We've already progressed
from questioning to torture.
Well what do you think terrifying trick
isn't it are those they're luca's fingers?
My turn to confess luca bit
the big one courtesy of our
aforementioned boss he didn't see
the use in keeping dead weight around
his fingers not again what did
he do damn it could he have
powers like that japanese tourist
oh and i'm not just a human lie
detector i have other tricks up
my sleeve as you've just seen for
yourself i can fit almost anything
inside your mouth for example
it'd be child's play to slide
that extinguisher between your
jaws of course if i did you'd be
joining Luca in the afterlife.
Now talk!
You know exactly who attacked Luca.
Were you paid to keep quiet?
Although I suppose it
doesn't really matter.
You'll still tell me what I want to know.
I guess that answers my question.
He definitely has powers.
You will tell me everything, or
the torture is going to intensify.
Jo no Jabaya!
This guy's deadly!
There's no other way.
If I want a chance in hell
at winning this fight,
I'm going to have to use Golden Wind!
Thank you.